Are you still using cursor? Yes, no,
maybe not because Claude card is now
more used by everyone at the YC and
every developer in the world. So, if you
don't, maybe you don't know there is
like composer 2.5 that it's probably the
best model out there right now. So, if
you don't use cursor, that's probably a
mistake. Isn't it, Mitchell?
>> Yeah, I made the biggest mistake then.
>> We we got to talk about that right now
and see if it's true or not. But,
composer 2.5 is shipped way cheaper than
Opus. It's way faster than Opus and
Codex all together and it's based on the
Chinese open-source model. So, that's
also interesting.
>> Here's [snorts] large composer 2.5 is
now available at Inkyusor and only
available in Inkyusor. You can't target
it on Open Router. It's a substan
substantial It's a substantial
improvement in intelligence and behavior
over composer two. It's It is better at
sustain work on long-running task,
follows complex instruction more re-
reliable
follows complex instruction more
reliable reliable
completion better.
>> Yeah, yeah, much better.
>> pleasant to collaborate with.
>> I don't care about that. Like, I don't
>> Listen and be smart.
>> Yeah, exactly. Like, just do what the
[__] I want and fix my bug.
>> Terminal bench 2.2, which is like the
CLI benchmark. Opus 4.7 69 and composer
69.3 and Opus is at 1.4.
>> That's nice.
>> GPT 5.5 82 and composer two 61. So,
yeah. Oh, GPT5 is at 82.
>> Yeah, yeah, I like GPT5.5.
>> Damn.
>> So, well, I think that's why they
compare with Opus.
>> These dimensions are not well captured
by existing benchmark, but we find that
they are better more for real real world
usefulness. Yeah, so of course they they
have created their own benchmark and
they are like at the top right.
>> Yeah. Well, I think that's always stupid
because if you create your own
benchmark, you're not going to lose on
it, right?
>> It's a good jump, but still behind Cloud
Code and GPT, but way cheaper. That's
interesting. 85% of the compute of
Composer 2.5 comes from additional
training and reinforcement learning.
Composer training and reinforcement
That's basically every action that it's
going through Cursor I'm putting in on
top of the model. So, basically what
they do is fine-tune Kimmy 2.5 and make
it better with all of the developer data
they have from the ID. And that's why
Elon Musk bought I put an option on
Cursor because all of that data can be
used on Grok.
>> Yeah, they have people paying them to
get a subscription to help them train
their own model.
>> Wait, they have other people paying them
to train them Yes.
>> Yeah, that's smart, right?
>> I mean, that's good.
>> I have a product we can make it better,
please pay me to do it.
>> Yeah, basically like together with
SpaceX we have trained a significant
larger model from scratch using 10x more
total compute. Yeah, Cursor says 2
millions with Cursor says 2 million H100
equivalent and all combined data of
training techniques. And so, from
artificial analysis, which is like a
benchmark, a third-party benchmark for
call this Composer 2.5, which is not so
bench, the last model in the Composer
line was called 62 on the coding agent
index of 40-point gain over Composer 2.
Let's put it on third place of all
tested agents behind only max. Oh, okay.
4.7 max in Cloud Code 66. Okay, there's
a gap. And GPT-5 XI reasoning in Codex
65. Okay, the cost 4 4 bucks and 10
cents and 482 per tax respectively. And
next the cost of Composer 2.5 fast.
Yeah, like at 40 cents, 44 cents, and
60x the cost of Composer 2.5 standard.
0.7.
>> So, then my question is, do Cloud Code
and Codex have so high margins, or are
they really making it so much better?
Yeah, if you if it's 60 times more
expensive to use the other ones, that's
a lot.
>> 463. Like for what we do, I don't think
we will see the difference in terms of
reasoning.
>> No, and even if you just let it run
triple, it's still so much cheaper and
doing it triple times or having three
agents doing the same thing, comparing
them, merging it, that gives you a
better quality and so much cheaper.
>> You can even use that for on a 20 bucks
subscription. If you can't pay 200 bucks
a month, then then you have a crazy good
model.
>> Yeah. Yeah, yeah. And for not for every
task need like a big model. A lot of
tasks are so simple to do.
>> And if it's fast, you just run it
multiple times. That's why also it's
good at agentic, right? Because yeah,
then you can run more in parallel. Still
go with like the 200 subscription, but
>> And you just give each agent a different
task.
>> Yeah.
>> Like one needs to double-check
everything and needs to question
everything, and the other one is for
security, and just have them merge all
the code and and improvements that they
can do.
>> Are you Yeah, if you have something like
like for example, you have a new
project, you can run cursor agents
composer on the on all of the GitHub
task and stuff. You start bootstrapping
and then you pull everything, you test
everything, and then Yeah, you can you
can have like some good asynchronous
work job
on that.
>> That can be a cheap good project, a good
setup.
>> Let's go by benchmark. Okay, so I look
legit. I mean, will that make you
redownload cursor?
>> Yep.
>> One day we're going to reach like a 99%
in every [__] benchmark whatsoever,
and getting like the the 10 more like
0.1 point on whatever benchmark coding
whatever will not matter at all. So
everyone will have their own model. So
maybe they will we will stop swapping,
use balls or whatever once we will it
will be like maxed out.
>> Yeah, then it it's more about what is
the easiest to use and the most stable
product.
>> Open claw got a lot of user. MS got a
lot more and like have the same growth
similar to growth because it was way
more stable and less than MS than open
claw itself. So, yeah. Maybe we can see
the same kind of movement for the
models, too.
>> Yeah, I think so. I think that's going
to matter a lot.
>> Yeah.
>> Because if we go up a lot more in points
so that we go towards 99, I think the
last points are only for people who do
the really complex work.
>> We're going to find vaccine against
cancer with like composer five.
>> Yeah, but people making WordPress
templates and and forms, they don't need
it.
>> Yeah, true. I was thinking about that
like we do like get back to Shopify
e-commerce like drop shipping stuff on
Shopify. And especially with like a
Shopify CLI, with the model that we have
now compared to what we had like one
year ago when we started to look at it.
>> Yeah, they didn't prove the entire game.
>> I mean, probably not going to be the
only one doing that and everyone on
Earth is doing the same freaking [__]
but like their game is probably way more
interesting right now. Continue training
on Munch AI open weight give me 2.5 as
with composer two with cursor reporting
85% of total compute from its own
additional training and run for small
learning. They are the only one with
this data. That's why they got bought by
Elon 10/60 billion. They tracked
everything. And I think that's that's
that's AI apps are very good exclusively
in cursor. Both cursor ID and cursor
CLI. External is not available.
>> Yeah, you need to have the cursor app.
>> Yeah. I cursor CLI, too. Yeah, okay. So,
if you have the cursor then you can in
that that's where it works. Like the T3
code front end is using cursor CLI. We
use the cursor models in another
interface.
>> Yeah, but then it should also be
possible to set up an API call to your
own Mac mini and use the cursor CLI to
get cheap API. Just host it yourself.
>> Some feedback on Reddit. The composer
2.5 is my new default. It's fast,
accurate, and actually cheap. Trying
myself to use GPT 5.5 for anything that
was not trivial. Try composer mostly
because I was curious and I didn't want
to burn credit on the other fixed this
link error loop. And it's good like it's
annoying good. I don't know how fast it
is. Stuff lands in the right file,
doesn't rewrite half of the module for
no reason, pick up weird pattern with
without me pasting three example every
time. Can I conclude already?
>> Yeah, we're not going to use it, but
thank you too.
>> Yeah, well, were you like at least
thinking about using it?
>> I mean, yeah, I was even thinking like
maybe I can get the 20 bucks
subscription so I can use cursor when I
completely out of open AI or Claude.
Like for this week, I think I'm good so
but especially with with the codex
resetting like the subscription every
now and then. It's happening every week
almost or every two three days. So
>> Yeah, if you use it at least only for
checking the code that was created by
codex, you can take out the opus, throw
it away, take the cheaper one, and have
that used.
>> Yeah. Yeah, and try try to
>> That will save you some money, but I'm
not I have a working setup. I'm happy
with pricing and they didn't convince me
yet to swap.
>> Yeah, I mean, I will try for you 20
bucks and then I will tell you
>> Whoa, use it. Use it.
>> Thank you cursor. If you want to sponsor
us because we said that your model are
great, uh please send us a check. We
take crypto.
My mutual, thank you so much for your
time.
>> Thank you too.
>> We will see you around. Bye-bye.
>> Bye.